Guide to the John Holmstrom Papers and Punk Magazine Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual materials, Series VIII
  - Videocassettes, 1990s-2000s (Box 118)
    - Racist cartoons, undated; GENMSS951_0006; 1; This videotape is not digitized. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672393)
      6. Warner Bros. "Angel Puss" (black child "Sambo" and white cat) - Chuck Jones
      7. Warner Bros. "Goldilocks and the Jivin' Bears" (three black bears do the jive and the wolf dances with Goldilocks)
      8. Warner Bros. "Scrap Happy Daffy" (black and white, anti-Nazi Daffy Duck becomes super American) - Cashlin
      9. Warner Bros. "The Ducktators" (war cartoon with Mussolini and Hitler and Chamberlain characters) - Norm McCabe
      10. Warner Bros. Bugs Bunny defense bonds promo (Bugs does black-face bit - Al Jolson)
      11. Warner Bros. "Coal Black and the Sebben Dwarves" (classic wartime cartoon) - Clampett
      12. Porky Pig - "Son of a Bitch"
      13. "Scrub Me Mama with a Boogie Beat" - Walter Lantz; jive-music cartoon "Lazy Town"
      14. "John Henry" puppettoon - George Pal; [?] folktale/fable
      15. "Jasper on a [Vana?]" puppettoon - George Pal; Peggy Lee vocal
      16. Amos & Andy in "Rassling Match"
      17. Amos & Andy on "The Lion Tamer"
      18. Warner Bros. "The Early Worm Gets the Bird"; incomplete, ends after a couple of minutes (crow birds)
    - Joey Ramones 50th Birthday Party at Hammerstein Ballroom, NYC, 1:68:00 raw footage (tape 1), 2001-05; GENMSS951_0007; 1; 02:45:02 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672401)
    - Warner Reprise Music Video, Sex Pistols, "The Great Rock 'n Roll Swindle", undated; GENMSS951_0008; 1; 01:40:10 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672419)
    - Dee Dee Ramone Tribute at the Continental, F#TV raw footage, 2002; GENMSS951_0009; 1; 00:39:15 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672427)
    - Iggy Pop Live, undated; GENMSS951_0010; 1; 02:42:00; After the segment on Iggy Pop, a poor quality Ramones video follows. After that, other better-quality Ramones video appears including a biographical video. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672435)
    - D.O.A., undated; GENMSS951_0011; 1; 01:37:00 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672443)
    - Punk Mag Show at CBGB's, raw footage, undated; GENMSS951_0012; 1; 01:10:40 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672450)
      A typed letter included with the tape reads: Hi John, Here is a tape with all the footage I got the night of the Punk Magazine show at CBGB's and the gallery. We had a blast playing and just being there was an experience. A few weeks after I saw the horn player that was in the band doing "My Generation". It was a PBS tribute to Doo-Wop and he was in the horn section. I can only hope to see Thor and Handsome Dick on the Food Network or Home Shopping Channel. Regards, Tommy White
    - The Fast and Under Underground (comp), undated; GENMSS951_0013; 1; 01:39:09 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672468)
    - Riff Rafferty, undated; GENMSS951_0014; 1; 00:46:18 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672476)
    - Iggy Pop, Live in Paris A L' Olympia, Part II of II, running time 52:44, transferred 2004; GENMSS951_0015; 1; 00:54:19; The tape has noise in the audio from time to time. The video is fair. There is a timecode that runs through the tape. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672484)
      "Iggy in Paris - Kiss My Blood" DVD recorded live @ the Olympia in Paris: 1991-03-15. Included with the tape is a list of tracks and song writers listed below.
      1. "Raw Power" - Iggy Pop, James Williamson
      2."Five Foot One" - Iggy Pop
      3. "Dirt" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      4. "Loose" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      5. "Lust for Life" - Iggy Pop, David Bowie
      6. "China Girl" - Iggy Pop, David Bowie
      7. "I Got a Right" - Iggy Pop
      8. "Butt Town" - Iggy Pop
      9. "Real Wild Child" - Johnny O'Keefe, Johnny Greenan, Dave Owens
      10. My Baby Wants to Rock and Roll - Iggy Pop, Slash
      11. "Neon Forest" - Iggy Pop
      12. "Home" - Iggy Pop
      13. "Brick by Brick" - Iggy Pop
      14. "1969" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      15. "Candy" - Iggy Pop
      16. "I Wanna Be Your Dog" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      17. "No Fun" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      18. "Search and Destroy" - Iggy Pop, James Williamson
      19. "Down on the Street" - Stooges AKA James Osterberg (Iggy Pop), Dave Alexander, Ron Asheton, Scott Asheton
      20. "The Passenger" - Iggy Pop, Ricky Gardner
      21. "Louie Louie" - Richard Berry
      22. "Foxy Lady" - Jimi Hendrix
    - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame, undated; GENMSS951_0016; 1; 02:01:13 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672492)
    - Jerry Springer "Holiday Hell: Feast IV"; Blondes (Blondie segment), Bizarre, episode 3000, undated; GENMSS951_0017; 1; This tape has not been digitized. There was no reference of Blondie found on this tape. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672500)
    - Iggy and The Stooges-Coachella, 1970-Cincinatti/Goose Lake/Dinah etc., undated; GENMSS951_0018; 1; 02:40:24 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672518)
    - The Stooges, Wantagh, NY at Jones Beach Theatre, 2003 August 8, 66 minutes; Iggy Pop, "La Rage De Virve-Arte TV" (SPAIN TV) 1997, 51 minutes. Lots of cool Iggy clips from the 1970s., 2003-08-08; GENMSS951_0019; 1; 01:57:41 (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672526)
    - D.O.A. timecoded, undated; GENMSS951_0020; 1; 01:35:36; A timecode runs through the entire tape. (Box 118, Item barcode 39002093672534)
  - 5 2 3/8" 300' tapes and 4 reel to reels, 1970s-1980s (Box 119)
- Computer media
  Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  - Computer media, 1990s-2000s; 11 CD-Rs (Box 120)